

Can Bartu Kılıç

Web & Mobile Developer

🐽 medium.com/@canbartuklc 📊 linkedin.com/in/cbartuk 🔗 cbartuk.com 🜓 Complete 😝 B / A

I am 28 years old and I live in Istanbul. I have been interested in electronics since childhood. This curiosity led me to make robots and to learn how to program them. I have focused rowing and enhancing my skillset consists of all these areas. My main goal in this field is being productive to solve real life problems by having a pragmatic mindset. Currently, I am advancing my career in web programming and mobile programming.

Education

HarvardX, M.M. Computer Science & Mobile Apps

2022 - 2023

Istanbul Arel University, B.D. Electric Electronic Engineer

2014 - 2019 Istanbul, Türkiye

Professional Experience

Mindstone Blockchain Labs., Frontend Engineer

02/2023 - 09/2024 Istanbul, Türkiye

- Atomic Design Patterns
- Web Accessibility
- · Make a Editor pages
- Make a Landing pages
- Make a NFT Game
- Cookie management

TECH STACK: Next JS | SCSS - Mixin, Function | Typescript ~ Javascript | Node JS | UI Kits | Git | Ether.js

Scouthub.io ~ NFT Game, Frontend Developer

06/2022 - 03/2023

Singapore

- Atomic Design Patterns
- Semantic Web
- Web Accessibility
- Single Page Applications

TECH STACK: React JS | Next JS | SCSS - Mixin, Function | Typescript ~ Javascript | Node JS | UI Kits | Git |

BiLira Technology Inc.

Blockchain Researcher

03/2022 - 06/2022

- Blockchain101 book authorship
- Article and social media writing
- Marketing and Brand Department content producer(Details are in the 'Projects' section)
- Event and seminar speaker as a company representative
- Improving brand awareness, managing influencer marketing processes

Operation Specialist

01/2022 - 03/2022 Istanbul, Türkiye

- Development of auxiliary tools and methods for continuous analysis and improvement of working processes
- Customer support processes related to products and services
- Monitoring of departmental activities

MD KALIP/ADAL PANO, R&D Engineer

07/2020 - 11/2021 Istanbul, Türkiye

- Robotic coding
- Practicing designer
- Functional application and production management
- Internal application development for quality control monitoring

TECH STACK: C++ | C# | Arduino | HTML | CSS | Javascript

Nevbahar MALL Uskudar(Kalyon & Noya Electric), Construction Manager

- Comprehensive project management and field coordinator
- Project design and management of creative teams
- Project link: https://nevbaharuskudar.com/

TECH STACK: AUTOCAD

Prysmian (Siemens) Group, Intern R&D Department

- Cable design on Autocad 3D
- Implementing engineer in Turkey submarine fiber cable systems project(I was in the field with the dives.)
- $\bullet \ \, \text{Project link:} \, \underline{\text{https://www.prysmiangroup.com/staticres/nexst-2017-4/article-6.html}} \, \, \mathscr{D} \,$

TECH STACK: AUTOCAD, SQL

Skills			
Typescript	• • • •	JavaScript	• • • • •
React.js	• • • • •	Next.js	• • • • •
Vue.js	• • • • •	Node.js	• • • • •
HTML / CSS	• • • • •	Solidity	• • • • •
Git	• • • • •	Kotlin	• • • • •
React Native	• • • • •	Business Development	• • • • •

Languages

English — PTE (Score: 56)

German — A2

Turkish — Native

Projects

All Projects

- <u>fbtokenofficial.com</u> *∂*
- Boomland.io ∂
- auction.themindstone.com @
- papir.ai 🔗
- app.scouthub.io ∂
- scouthub.io ∂

Academic

Trainings and Seminars I Provide

- İstanbul Üniversitesi İktisat Fakültesi Blockchain A.M.A. Etkinliği 🔗
- Solidity Workshop #1 #2 Ø
- Beykent Üniversitesi BUTechDays'22 ∂
- İstanbul Üniversitesi Cerrahpaşa Mühendislik Fakültesi NFT101 Eğitim 🔗
- <u>Çukurova Üniversitesi Blockchain101 Eğitim</u> ∂
- Türk Alman Üniversitesi Blockchain101 Eğitim 🔗

Certificates

- JavaScript (Basic) ∅
- SQL (Basic) Ø
- FE Web Dev (Patika) ∅

- Java (Basic) ∂
- Kotlin 101 *⊘*
- FE Dev 200 (BilgeAdam) ∅

References

Ayhan Güneş, *Owner*, Ford Otomotiv & Fibro Türkiye agunes@enderltd.com

Mustafa Morbel, *Senior Frontend Dev., Instructor*, BilgeAdam Academy +90 532 705 1088

10/2018 – 05/2020 Istanbul, Türkiye

06/2017 - 09/2017

Bursa, Türkiye